https://www.absolutesound.com.sg/privacy-policy

Contact Us/
Shop Online/Audio Bar by Absolute SoundAudioquest on LazadaFocal on Lazada
Bringing you closer to music.
Contact Us/
Shop Online/Audio Bar by Absolute SoundAudioquest on LazadaFocal on Lazada
This Privacy Policy sets out how Absolute Sound Distribution Pte Ltd, (referred to herein as “Absolute Sound”, “us”, “we” or “our”) comply with the provisions of the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 of Singapore (“PDPA”). At Absolute Sound, your privacy is of extreme importance to us. This Privacy Policy outlines way in which we collect, use, disclose and/ or retain your Personal Data. The Privacy Policy sets out:how we manage your Personal Data;the types of Personal Data we collect, use, disclose and/ or retain;how we collect, use, disclose and/ or retain your Personal Data; andthe purpose(s) for which we collect, use, disclose and/ or retain your Personal Data.Your Personal DataIn this Privacy Policy, “Personal Data” refers to any data and/or information about you from which you can be identified by, either (a) from that data; or (b) from that data and other information to which we may have legitimate access to. Examples of such Personal Data include but are not limited to:your name, NRIC, passport or other identification number, telephone number(s), mailing address, email address and any other information relating to you which you have provided in any forms you may have submitted to use, or in other forms of interaction with you;information relating to payments, such as your bank account number;information about your usage of and interaction with our website and/ or services including computer and connection information, device capability, bandwidth, statistics on page views and traffic to and from our websiteCollection of your Personal DataWe may collect your Personal Data through the following ways:when you purchase at any of Absolute Sound Stores;when you access our websites or perform an online transaction;when you respond to our request for additional Personal Data;when you ask to be included in an email or other mailing list;when you request that we contact you;when you respond to our initiatives or promotions; andwhen you submit your Personal Data to us for any other reason.When you browse our website, you do so anonymously. Please refer to Section 5 on web cookies.Purposes for the Collection, Use and Disclosure of Your Personal DataWe may collect, use, disclosure and/ or retain your Personal Data for the following purposes:to assist you with your enquiries;to process payment for your purchases;to improve membership/ customer services, such as resolving complaints and handling requests and enquiries;to conduct research, surveys and interviews;to keep you updated on our news, events and promotions; andto comply with applicable laws and regulations.We may provide individually identifiable information to third parties in cases where it is required by law, or we may provide your personal information to our legal or tax advisors for business purposes. It is Absolute Sound's policy not to disclose any personal information about site users to third parties without specific permission to do so. Absolute Sound does not sell or disclose any of your personal information to marketers or periodical publishers.Marketing Purposes From time to time, we may contact you via mail, electronic mail, telephone (call or SMS-Text), facsimile or social media platforms, to inform you about our mailing list benefits, promotions, services and events that we think may be of interest to you.You can let us know at any time if you no longer wish to receive marketing materials (by informing us by email) and we will remove your details from our direct marketing database.Please note that we may still send you non-marketing messages such as e-receipts, surveys, customer-service notices and other service related notices.Use of Cookies We may collect or analyse anonymised information from which individuals cannot be identified, such as number of users and their frequency of use, the number of page views (or page impressions) that occur on our website and common entry and exit points into our website. We make use of “cookies” to store and track information when you enter our website. Such cookies are used to track information such as the number of users and their frequency of use. Cookies do not reveal or contain any personal information, nor can they read any information on your computer or interact with other cookies on your hard drive. Such aggregate Information collected may be used to assist us in analysing the usage of our website so as to improve your online experience with us.Should you wish to disable the cookies associated with these technologies you may do so by changing the setting on your browser. However, please note that this may affect the functionality of the website.Acceptance and ConsentBy using this website, you signify acceptance and agreement with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any one or more of our terms, please discontinue use of this site.By submitting information to Absolute Sound, you consent to the collection, use, disclosure and retention of that information for the purposes described to you at the time of collection, or as outlined in this Privacy Policy.If you have questions or concerns about your personal information or if you wish to stop receiving information about Absolute Sound or have your comments removed from our website and/ or social media platforms, please contact us in writing or email.     7. External LinksThis site contains links to other websites and Absolute Sound has no control over the content of third party sites and is not responsible for the privacy policies of such sites, nor for any information contained on those sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of such third party sites prior to disclosing any of your personal information.We reserve the right to update and amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any amendments to this Policy via announcements on our website or other appropriate means. If we amend this Policy, the amendment will only apply to personal data collected after we have posted the revised Policy.
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
Sign Up
We respect your privacy.
Thank you!
Absolute SoundAbout UsPartnershipsArticlesFAQ
Privacy Policy
Services0% Instalment PlansShop OnlineAudio Bar by Absolute SoundFocal on LazadaAudioquest on LazadaSupportPurchase PolicesSubmit Support TicketAbsolute Sound Distribution represents the top premium home audio brands in the high fidelity industry. We carry a wide variety of audio products for home entertainment system for you to better experience your favourite music, movies and tv shows. Need help in choosing the right amplifier, speakers, cd player or building a home cinema system? Speak to us and we will help you customize and personalise the best system for you.We are the official authorised distributor for AudioQuest, Boulder, dCS, Custom Design, Elipson, Esoteric,  Focal, FM Acoustics, InAkustik, Isoacoustics, Magnepan, Meridian Audio, Naim Audio, Neat Acoustics, NorStone, Stenheim, Storm Audio, Sumiko, Teac, Thixar Audio and Transrotor. These brands are highly regarded and trusted in the electronics and speakers industry over the years.
